Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2, 1813-1991
5583/2
Kheel Center
74 linear ft.
Records, publications.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Publications, manuals, policies, and plans issued by a large sample of Fortune 500 corporations and by a variety of organizations, such as professional and trade associations, government agencies, and educational and cultural organizations. The materials issued by corporations include company histories, employee newsletters, employee benefit plans, personnel practice manuals, performance appraisal forms, affirmative action policies, training brochures, job descriptions, and career development programs as well as national trade association documents and recruitment material.
Several economic activities(sectors) are represented in the collection, such as manufacturing, transportation, mining, banking, insurance, utilities, trade, and services. Corporations whose pamphlets are held in the collection include AT&T, Bethlehem Steel, Bell Telephone System, Firestone Tire & Rubber, Ford Motor Co., General Electric, General Foods, General Mills, General Motors, Goodyear Tire & Rubber, Heinz, International Harvester, Johnson & Johnson, Lockheed Aircraft Co., Maytag Co., Metropolitan Life Insurance Co., National Association of Manufacturers, Pennsylvania Railroad Co., Radio Corporation of America (RCA), Standard Oil, Tennessee Valley Authority, Union Carbide, and Westinghouse Electric among numerous other corporations.
SUBJECTS
Names:
A. Kimball Company.; B.F. Goodrich Company.; Civil Service Commission of the City of New York.; Council of Retail Merchants (Ohio); Eli Lilly and Company.; General Electric Company. Erie Works (Erie, PA).; General Electric Company. River Works (Lynn, Mass.); General Electric Company. Pittsfield Works (Pittsfield, Mass.); General Foods Corporation.; General Mills, inc.; General Motors Corporation.; General Motors Corporation. Delco Products Division.; General Petroleum Corporation.; General Shoe Corporation.; General Telephone & Electronics Corporation.; General Telephone Company of California.; General Telephone Company of Indiana.; General Telephone Company of Michigan.; General Telephone Corporation.; Geneva Steel (Firm); Gerber Products Company.; Glass Container Manufacturers Institute.; Glenshaw Glass Company.; Globe Ticket Company.; Goodyear Atomic Corporation.; Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company.; Grand Union Company.; Graphic Arts Employers of America.; Grumman Aircraft Engineering Corporation.; Guaranty Trust Company of New York.; H.J. Heinz Company.; Hallmark Cards, Inc.; Haloid Company.; Haloid Xerox, Inc.; Harris Trust and Savings Bank.; Harris-Intertype Corp.; Harris-Seybold Company.; Harvard University.; Hawaii Employers Council.; Hawaiian Pineapple Co.; Hercules Incorporated.; Honeywell Inc.; Hotpoint.; Illinois Bell Telephone Company.; Illinois Central Industries.; Illinois Central Railroad Company.; Imperial Chemical Industries, ltd.; Imperial Oil Limited.; Industrial Accident Prevention Associations.; Industrial Association of San Francisco.; Industrial Hygiene Council.; Industrial Hygiene Foundation of America.; Ingersoll-Rand Company.; Inland Steel Company.; Institute of Life Insurance (New York, N.Y.); Institute of Management & Labor Relations.; International Business Machines Corporation.; International Nickel Company.; International Paper Company.; John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company.; Johns-Manville Corporation.; Johnson & Johnson.; Johnson Wax.; Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation.; Kaiser Steel Corporation.; Kennecott Copper Corporation.; Kimberly-Clark Corporation.; Koppers Company.; Kroger Company.; Leeds and Northrup Company.; Lever Brothers Company.; Libby, McNeill & Libby.; Libby-Owens Company.; Libby-Owens-Ford Glass Company.; Liberty Mutual Insurance Company.; Liggett & Myers Tobacco Company.; Lincoln Electric Company.; Lincoln Telephone & Telegraph Company.; Lockheed Aircraft Corporation.; Lukens Steel Company.; Lumberman's Industrial Relations Committee.; Manufacturers Hanover Trust Company.; Marathon Corporation.; Marathon Oil Company.; Marquette Cement Manufacturing Company.; Marquette University.; Marshall Field & Company.; Maytag Corporation.; McCord Corporation.; McGraw-Hill Book Company.; McGraw-Hill Companies.; McGraw-Hill Publishing Company.; McKesson and Robbins, inc.; McMurray Company.; Mead Corporation.; Mead Johnson & Company.; Merchants and Manufacturers Association.; Merck & Co.; Meredith Publishing Group.; Merrill Lynch, Pierce, Fenner & Beane.; Mesta Machine Company.; Metropolitan Life Insurance Company.; Michigan Bell Telephone Company.; Michigan Central Railroad Company.; Michigan. Civil Rights Commission.; Michigan. Civil Service Commission.; Michigan. Department of Labor.; Michigan. Department of Social Services.; Michigan. Labor Mediation Board.; Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Company.; Mobil Chemical Company.; Mobil Oil Corporation.; Mobil Overseas Oil Company.; Mobil Research and Development Corporation.; Mohawk Airlines.; Monroe Calculation Machine Company.; Monsanto Chemical Company.; Montgomery Ward.; Motorola, inc.; Mutual Life Insurance Company of New York.; Nash-Kelvinator Corporation.; National Academy of Arbitrators.; National Association of Broadcasters.; National Association of Foremen.; National Association of Furniture Manufacturers.; National Association of Manufacturers (U.S.); National Biscuit Company.; National Broadcasting Company.; National Cash Register Company.; National Coal Association.; National Committee for Full Employment (U.S.); National Consumers' League.; National Council on the Aging.; National Education Association of the United States; National Electrical Manufacturers Association.; National Farmers' Union (U.S.); National Foremen's Institute.; National Industrial Council (U.S.); National Management Association (U.S.); National Metal Trades Association (U.S.); National Restaurant Association (U.S.); National Restaurant Managers Association (U.S.); National Safety Council; National Society of Professional Engineers.; National Steel Corporation.; National Urban League.; New England Electric System.; New England Powers Association.; New England Telephone and Telegraph Company.; New Jersey Bell Telephone Company.; New Jersey Manufacturers Association.; New Jersey. Department of Civil Service.; New York (N.Y.). Department of Personnel.; New York (State). Temporary Commission Against Discrimination.; New York (State). Department of Civil Service.; New York (State). Department of Labor.; New York (State). Public Employment Relations Board.; New York (State). Workmen's Compensation Board.; New York Central Railroad Company.; New York Shipping Association.; New York State Electric and Gas Corporation.; New York Stock Exchange.; New York Telephone Company.; New York Times Company.; North American Aviation, inc.; Northeastern University (Boston, Mass.); Northwest Packers and Growers, inc.; Northwestern Bell Telephone Company.; Nunn-Bush Shoe Company.; Ohio Oil Company.; Ontario Hydro.; Organization Resources Counselors, Inc.; Owens-Corning Fiberglas Corporation.; Owens-Illinois Glass Company.; P.H. Hanes, Knitting Company.; Pacific Gas and Electric Company.; Pacific Power and Light Company.; Penn Central Merger Information Committee.; Penn Central Transportation Company.; Pennsylvania Railroad.; Peoples Gas Light and Coke Company.; Personnel Management Association of New York.; Personnel Management Association of the Northeast.; Personnel Management Association, inc.; Pfizer Inc.; Philadelphia Gas Works.; Philadelphia Rapid Transit Company.; Philadelphia Transportation Company.; Philip Morris and Company.; Phillips Petroleum Company.; Pillsbury Mills, Inc.; Pitney-Bowes, inc.; Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company.; Port of New York Authority.; Potomac Electric Power Company.; Potomac Sand & Gravel.; Procter & Gamble Company.; Prudential Insurance Company of America.; Public Personnel Association.; Public Service Corporation of New Jersey.; Public Service Electric and Gas Company.; State University of New York.; Theo. Hamm Brewing Company.; Thomas Macy & Co.; University of Hawaii (Honolulu). Industrial Relations Center.; University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign. Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations.; University of Michigan.; University of Minnesota.; University of Minnesota. Industrial Relations Center.; University of Mississippi.
Subjects:
Adult education; Aeronautics; Agricultural industries; Aluminum industry and trade; Airlines; Aircraft industry; Agricultural machinery; Architectural metal-work; Automobile industry and trade; Arbitration, Industrial; Agricultural chemicals industry; Audio equipment industry; Bituminous materials industry; Building trades; Buildings--Environmental engineering; Banks and banking; Breweries; Baked products industry; Business consultants; Clothing trade; Coal mines and mining; Chemical industry; Compressor industry; Clerks (Retail trade); Computer industry; Cereal products; Consumer protection; Container industry; Credit unions; Clay industries; Cement industries; Copper alloys; Dairy products industry; Detergent industry; Executives--Training of; Electric power transmission; Electronics industries; Food industry and trade; Frozen foods and industry; Footwear industry; Fruit trade; Farm produce--Marketing--Government policy; Finance, Public; Glass container industry; Glass manufacture; Gas extraction; Grain trade; Grocery trade; Gasket industry; Human capital; Hydroelectric power plants; Life insurance.; Iron industry and trade; Property insurance.; Casualty insurance.; Instructional materials industry; Health insurance.; Investment banking; Infant formula industry; Knit good industry; Labor unions; Local transit; Luggage industry; Logging; Medical supplies industry; Medicaid; Motor vehicle industry; Metal trade; Meat industry and trade; Military vehicle industry; Medical instruments and apparatus industry; Management; Measuring instruments; Natural gas pipelines; Notions (Merchandise); Newspaper publishing; Navigation equipment industry; National security; Office management; Office equipment and supplies; Petroleum refineries; Photographic industry; Paper folding (Graphic design); Public utilities; Paper products industry; Political participation; Plastics industry and trade; Pharmaceutical industry; Paint industry and trade; Public administration; Public opinion polls; Paper bag industry; Retail trade; Rug and carpet industry; Railroads; Rubber industry and trade; Railroad equipment industry; Roller bearings; Security systems industry; Service industries; Social security; Shipment of goods; Sanitary supply industry; Soybean industry; Slaughtering and slaughter-houses; Transportation equipment industry.; Telecommunication.; Trucking industry.; Trucks--Design and construction.; Textile industry.; Trade associations.; Tobacco industry.; Universities and colleges.; Vocational education.; Wood products.; Welding equipment industry.; Woolen goods industry.
Form and Genre Terms:
Records.; Publications
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related Collections:
5880: Archives Organization File V, Additional Company Documents
5583/1: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3
5583/4: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 4. Corporate and Organizational Publications
5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5
5583/6: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6
5956: Archives Organization File Additional records
CONTAINER LIST
- Box: 1, Folder: 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Your Group Insurance, 1859; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: J.N. Adam and Co. Personnel Services
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Vol. 8, No. 1, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Administrative Management Society
    Notes: January
  - Item 2: Vol. 8, No. 2, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: February
  - Item 3: Vol. 8, No. 3, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: March
  - Item 4: Vol. 8, No. 4, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: April
  - Item 5: Vol. 8, No. 6, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: June
  - Item 6: Vol. 8, No.7, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: September
  - Item 7: Vol. 8, No. 8, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: October
  - Item 8: Vol. 8, No. 9, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: November
  - Item 9: Vol. 8, No. 10, 1970; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: December
  - Item 10: Vol. 9, No. 1, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Vol. 9, No. 2, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Vol. 9, No. 3, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Vol. 9, No. 8, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Vol. 9, No. 9, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Vol. 9, No. 10, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Vol. 10. No. 1, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Vol. 10, No. 2, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Vol. 10, No.3, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Vol. 10, No. 4, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Vol. 10, No. 5, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: May
  - Item 21: Vol. 10, No.6, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: June-July
- Box: 1, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Morale Survey, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Author: Aeroquip Corporation
    Notes: July 27
- Box: 1, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Aerospace Industry, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: Karl G. Harr, Jr.
    Notes: Sept. 1
- Box: 1, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan for Employees of the First National Bank of Portland, 1942-1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: AETNA Life Insurance Company-Personnel Services
    Notes: July 1, 1942-January 1, 1951
- Box: 1, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Agway People, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: Agway, INC.
    Notes: April May June: Spring
  - Item 2: Agway People, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: April May June Spring
  - Item 3: Agway People, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: Jan. Feb. Mar. Winter
- Box: 1, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Author: Air Reduction Company
  - Item 2: Economic Security After Retirement, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Box: 1, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Airline Newsletter, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: Air Transport Association of America
    Notes: Fall
  - Item 2: Airline Newsletter, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Airline Newsletter, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Airline Newsletter, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: Winter
  - Item 5: Airline Newsletter, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: Summer
  - Item 6: Airline Newsletter, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Airline Newsletter, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Airline Newsletter, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Airline Newsletter, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Airline Newsletter, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Airline Newsletter, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: Spring
  - Item 12: Airline Newsletter, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: Airline Newsletter, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: Airline Newsletter, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Box: 1, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Modern Business Service, 1916; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Author: Ronald P. Falkner
- Box: 1, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Protection for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Alexander Smith and Sons Carpet Company
  - Item 2: A Description of the Pension Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Preview of Your Retirement, 1951; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: January 1st
  - Item 4: Protection for Production and Maintenance Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Box: 1, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Starscene, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Allegheny-Ludlum Industries
    Notes: Vol. 7, No. 2 Feb. 24th
  - Item 2: Starscene, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Vol. 7, No. 2
  - Item 3: Starscene, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Vol. 8, No. 9 August 19
  - Item 4: Starscene, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Starscene, 1978; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Vol. 9, No. 2 Feb.
  - Item 6: Starscene, 1978; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Vol. 9, No. 2
  - Item 7: Environment News, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: August 25
  - Item 8: Environment News, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Allegheny-Ludlum News, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Nov. 2-4
  - Item 10: Allegheny-Ludlum News, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Box: 1, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Salaried Employees Vacation Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Allied Chemical Corporation
    Notes: May 15, 1961
  - Item 2: Salaried Employees Long Term Disability Insurance Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: March 2, 1964
  - Item 3: Salaried Employees Group Life Insurance Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: Dec. 1, 1958
  - Item 4: Salaried Employees Major Medical Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Packaged Protection, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Blue Cross Blue Shield
    Notes: Nov.
  - Item 8: Salaried Employees Pension Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: Dec. 31, 1958
- Box: 1, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan for Employees, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: Allied Kid Company
    Notes: Jan 1
- Box: 1, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Emlpoyee's Retirement Plan, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Author: Allied Products, INC.
    Notes: Jan. 1
- Box: 1, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Retired Employees' Recreation Club, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Author: Allis- Chalmers
    Notes: Oct.
  - Item 2: Engineering Review Electric Utility Issue, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: Vol. 38, No. 1
  - Item 3: Pit and Quarry Annual Cement Issue, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Author: Allis-Chalmers Cement and Mining Systems
    Notes: July
  - Item 4: Engineering Review Electric Utility Issue, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: Vol. 39, No. 2
  - Item 5: Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Author: Fiat-Allis
    Notes: Vol. 38, No. 2
  - Item 6: Engineering Review, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Author: Allis Chalmers
    Notes: Vol. 40, No. 2
  - Item 7: Program for October 1955, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Author: Retired Employees Recreation Club
  - Item 8: Engineerig Review/Electric Utility Issue, 1973; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Pit and Quarry Annual Cement Issue, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Author: Allis Chalmers Cement and Minig Systems
  - Item 10: Engineering Review/Electric Utility Issue, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: Reporter, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Author: Allis-Chalmers
- Box: 1, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Bicentennial Report: A Report on the Realization of a Dream, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Author: The Amalgamated Banks
  - Item 2: Statement of Condition, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Author: Amalgamated Bank of New York
    Notes: January, 31, 1947
  - Item 3: Banking Institutions Founded by the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Author: Amalgamated Bank of New York: Amalgamated Trust and Savings Bank Chicago
  - Item 4: Statement of Condition, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: Dec. 31,1962
  - Item 5: Statement of Condition, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: Dec. 31, 1962
  - Item 6: Statement of Condition, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Statement of Condition, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Statement of Condition, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: Dec. 31, 1960
  - Item 9: Statement of Condition, 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: Statement of Condition, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: Dec. 31, 1957
  - Item 11: Bicentennial Report: A Report on the Realization of a Dream, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 12: Statement of Condition, 1956; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Author: The Amalgamated Bank of New York
    Notes: dec. 31, 1956
  - Item 13: The Story of a Bank, 1923-1963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 14: The Story of a Bank, 1923-1963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Box: 1, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan for Employees, 1942; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Author: Amalgamated Sugar Company
    Notes: March 1, 1942
- Box: 1, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Scope, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Author: Amerada Hess
    Notes: May/June
  - Item 2: Scope, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Annual Report, 1977; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: The Business of Amerada Hess, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: The People of Amerada Hess, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Box: 1, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Comprhensive Medical Expense Insurance Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Author: Amerada Petroleum Corporation and Subsidies
    Notes: May 1, 1963
  - Item 2: Employees' Savings and Stock Bonus Plan, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: July 1, 1952
  - Item 3: Employees' Retirement Income Plan, 1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: Sept. 1, 1944
- Box: 1, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Flagship News, 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Author: American Airlines, Inc.
    Notes: Vol. 31, No. 3 Feb. 2, 1976
  - Item 2: The Most Non-Stops to Success, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Box: 1, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Suggestions Systems Manual, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Author: American Airlines Communications Suggestions Systems
    Notes: Nov. 3
  - Item 2: Get An Idea!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Author: American Airlines Employees Suggestion Blank
  - Item 3: Your Part in the Suggestion System, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Author: American Airlines Communications Suggestin Systems
- Box: 1, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: An Engineering Career for Your School-Age Child, 1956; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Author: John S. Lampe
- Box: 1, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Consumer Arbitration Advisory Council, 1978; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Author: Natinal Center for Dispute Settlement of the American Arbitration Association
- Box: 1, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)